<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container version="2">
  <!--
    WackyNAS Network Dashboard - Community Apps Template
    Submitted to: https://github.com/Squidly271/AppFeed
  -->

  <n>WackyNAS Network Dashboard</n>
  <Repository>WackyRazzy/unraid-network-dashboard</Repository>
  <Registry>https://github.com/WackyRazzy/unraid-network-dashboard</Registry>
  <Branch>main</Branch>
  <Category>Network: Tools: Status: Other:</Category>
  <TemplateURL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/WackyRazzy/unraid-network-dashboard/main/template/network-dashboard.xml</TemplateURL>
  <Icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/WackyRazzy/unraid-network-dashboard/main/assets/icon.png</Icon>
  <Overview>
WackyNAS Network Dashboard is a real-time network monitoring plugin for Unraid that adds a live widget to your Unraid Dashboard and a full-page cyberpunk-style diagnostic panel at http://YOUR-IP:8888.

Features:
- Dashboard widget showing public IP, ISP, ASN, location, latency and Tailscale status
- Full diagnostic panel with dark cyberpunk UI at port 8888
- Public IP, ISP name, ASN number and location detection
- Proxy and VPN detection on your internet connection
- Ping latency bars to Cloudflare (1.1.1.1), Google (8.8.8.8), Quad9 (9.9.9.9) and your gateway
- Local port status checker for HTTP, HTTPS, SSH, DNS, Plex and more
- Physical network interface table (eth0, bond0, br0, Tailscale)
- Docker running and stopped container counts plus RX/TX stats
- Lightweight Python3 API server - no extra packages needed
- Auto-starts on every Unraid boot via /boot/config/go
  </Overview>
  <Description>
Real-time network monitoring plugin for Unraid. Adds a dashboard widget and a full-page diagnostic panel (port 8888) showing public IP, ISP, latency, port status, network interfaces, Tailscale VPN, and Docker stats. Lightweight Python3 server that auto-starts on boot with zero extra dependencies.
  </Description>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:8888</WebUI>
  <Support>https://github.com/WackyRazzy/unraid-network-dashboard/issues</Support>
  <Project>https://github.com/WackyRazzy/unraid-network-dashboard</Project>
  <MinVer>6.12.0</MinVer>
  <Changes>
### 2025.03.08 ###
- Initial public release
- Real-time network dashboard widget on Unraid main page
- Full diagnostic panel with public IP, ISP, latency, ports, interfaces
- Python3 API server on port 8888
- Auto-start on boot via /boot/config/go
  </Changes>
</Container>
